

CONTACT ME

- © +60 1136492732
- in www.linkedin.com/in/evavdavid
- S Iban, Malay, English, Japanese

PROFILE

Through these recent years, I have been trying to cultivate 'Growth Mindset' in me. Growth mindset is all about believing that skills can be cultivated through efforts. By far, this mindset has been helping me to reframe any obstacles as opportunities to learn and grow as a person.

HARD SKILLS

- Japanese: Speaking, **Writing & Reading**
- Microsoft Office: Word, **Powerpoint & Excel**
- **Public Speaking**

RECENT ACHIEVEMENTS

- Japanese Language Proficiency Test (JLPT - N1 Level)
- Completed Advanced **Japanese Business** Communication Course

Grant Winner of Rotary Yoneyama Memorial **Master Course**

Scholarship

EVA VANESSA ANAK DAVID

→ CURRENT LOCATION: MIRI. SARAWAK

WORK EXPERIENCES

2023 - Present

Trust & Safety Associate (Japanese Speaker) at Accenture Technology Solutions, Selangor

As a Content Moderator specializing in App Quality Review, I play a pivotal role in ensuring the excellence and integrity of mobile applications. My responsibilities included meticulous examination and evaluation of app appearance, content, and overall user experience to maintain high standards and compliance with industry guidelines.

2021 - 2023

Part time job as Teaching Assistant at Niigata University of International and **Information Studies (NUIS)**

I set up equipments and helped the lecturers to prepare the classroom for English classes. Through this part time job, I was able to develop a good rapport with Japanese students while improving my communication skills.

2021 - 2022

Part time job as Inventory Staff at AJIS Co., Ltd.

(Based in Niigata Prefecture)

I travelled to various retail locations, scanned products in different areas of the store and recorded totals in a timely manner. I also performed quality checks on stored inventory and discarded inventory that does not meet the company's standards.

EDUCATION

2021 - 2023

Master's Degree in Applied Chemistry

Niigata University Ikarashi Campus, Niigata Prefecture, Japan

2019 - 2021

Bachelor's Degree in Chemistry and Chemical Engineering

2016 - 2019

Niigata University Ikarashi Campus, Niigata Prefecture, Japan

Diploma in Material Engineering

Ibaraki National Institute of Technology, Ibaraki Prefecture, Japan